import 'package:quizzler/Question.dart';

class QuizBrain {
  int _questionNumber = 0;
  int getQuestionNumber() {
    return _questionNumber;
  }

  int getBankLength() {
    return _QuestionBank.length;
  }

  List<Question> _QuestionBank = [
    Question(questionText: "A slug's blood is green.", questionAnswer: false),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.",
        questionAnswer: true),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "The total surface area of two human lungs is approximately 70 square metres.",
        questionAnswer: true),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.",
        questionAnswer: true),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are technically entitled to a state funeral, because the building is considered too sacred a place.",
        questionAnswer: false),
    Question(
        questionText: "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.",
        questionAnswer: true),
    Question(
        questionText: "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.",
        questionAnswer: false),
    Question(
        questionText: "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.",
        questionAnswer: true),
    Question(
        questionText: "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.",
        questionAnswer: true),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "The loudest sound produced by any animal is 188 decibels. That animal is the African Elephant.",
        questionAnswer: false),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.",
        questionAnswer: false),
    Question(
        questionText:
            "Chocolate affects a dog's heart and nervous system; a few ounces are enough to kill a small dog.",
        questionAnswer: true)
  ];
  void nextQuestion() {
    if (_questionNumber < _QuestionBank.length - 1) {
      _questionNumber++;
    }
  }

  bool getCorrectAnswer() {
    return _QuestionBank[_questionNumber].questionAnswer;
  }

  String getQuestionText() {
    return _QuestionBank[_questionNumber].questionText;
  }
}
